{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"8.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"2017 SLCH Contractor Orientation","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":4380,"frameRate":30},"ContentStructure":[{"id":"Click_Box_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_4","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_4","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_280","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_280","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_335","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Please click SUBMIT after entering your name and use the playbar below to navigate the orientation.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4607","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"Slide 1","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_1","Text_Entry_Box_4","Text_Entry_Button_4","Text_Caption_280","Text_Caption_335"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4607"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_2","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4619","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"Safety is Everyone’s Business ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4619"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_3","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4631","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"SLCH Golden Rules ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_3"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4631"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4643","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"Hospital Safety Rules (HSRs) ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_4"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4643"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4655","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"WORKING WITH A CURRENT RISK ASSESSMENT ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_5"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4655"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_6","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4667","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"INFECTION CONTROL ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_6"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4667"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4679","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"LIFE SAFETY ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4679"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4691","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"HOT WORK ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_8"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4691"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4703","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"HAZARDOUS ENERGY SOURCES ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4703"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_10","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4715","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"TOOL SAFETY ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4715"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_11","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4727","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"CONFINED SPACES ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_11"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4727"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_12","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4739","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"TEMPORARY CONTAINMENT AREAS ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_12"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4739"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_13","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4751","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"MRI SAFETY ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_13"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4751"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_14","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4763","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"WORKING FROM HEIGHTS ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_14"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4763"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_15","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4775","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"INDOOR AIR QUALITY ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4775"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_16","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4787","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"EMERGENCY NOTIFICATION ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_16"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4787"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_17","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4799","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"HAZARD COMMUNICATION ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_17"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4799"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_18","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4811","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"HAZARDOUS MATERIALS AND WASTE ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4811"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_19","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4823","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"BLOODBORNE PATHOGENS ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_19"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4823"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_20","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4835","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"NO SMOKING ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4835"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_21","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4847","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"NO DRUGS OR ALCOHOL ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_21"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4847"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_22","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4859","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"NO WEAPONS ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_22"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4859"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_23","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4871","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"KEY SLCH CONTACTS ","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_23"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4871"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_24","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide4883","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"Slide 24","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_24"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4883"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_25","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_314","title":"Be sure to Click Submit after each question.  Advance by clicking Next.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Animation_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Animation_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_336","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"That’s two clicks! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4895","class":"PPTX Slide","instance":"Slide 25","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_25","Text_Caption_314","Animation_1","Text_Caption_336"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":240},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4895"}}},{"id":"si1251","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5556q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5556q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_287","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5660","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5582","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What sections can be found in a Risk Assessment? (select any or all that apply) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5604","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5608","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Pre-Work H&S Checklist  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5604a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Pre-Work H&S Checklist\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5615","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5619","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Infections Control Risk Assessment (ICRA)    ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5615a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Infections Control Risk Assessment (ICRA)\r\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5824","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5828","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interim Life Safety Measures (ILSM)  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5824a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Interim Life Safety Measures (ILSM)\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5839","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5843","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Electrical Safety Investigations, Work Conditions, and Permits  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5839a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5854","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5858","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All the above  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5854a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All the above\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5656","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5664","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5556q0","for":"Slide5556q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5678","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide5556q0","for":"Slide5556q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide5556q0","for":"Slide5556q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5645","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5556","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_287","si5582","si5589","si5608","si5619","si5828","si5843","si5858","si5664","si5678","si10737","si5645"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5556"},"question":{"interactionId":"5569","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"What sections can be found in a Risk Assessment?\r(select any or all that apply)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_315","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_315","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","roles":{}},{"id":"si11273","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_279","roles":{}},{"id":"si11285","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_282","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11297","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_283","title":"Where must a contractor obtain a hot work permit? (select one) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11308","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_286","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_288","title":"Public Safety   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11308a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"160","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Public Safety\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11319","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_289","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_290","title":"EHS Department    ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11319a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"162","roles":{"answer":{"title":"EHS Department\r\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si11330","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_291","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11334","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_292","title":"Facilities  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11330a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"164","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Facilities \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11341","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_293","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11345","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_294","title":"Superintendent   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11341a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"166","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Superintendent \r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11412","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_79","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11464q1","for":"Slide11464q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11426","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_81","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide11464q1","for":"Slide11464q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11440","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_82","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide11464q1","for":"Slide11464q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11454","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_83","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide11464q1","for":"Slide11464q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_295","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11376","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_296","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11388","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_297","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11464","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_315","si11285","si11297","si11312","si11323","si11334","si11345","si11412","si11426","si11440","si11454","si11388"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11464"},"question":{"interactionId":"11265","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Where must a contractor obtain a hot work permit? (select one)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_316","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","roles":{}},{"id":"si6173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","roles":{}},{"id":"si6185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"Contractors are responsible for disposing of all remaining hazardous chemicals or waste. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6208","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6212","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"True  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6208a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"False   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6219a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6364q2","for":"Slide6364q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6326","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide6364q2","for":"Slide6364q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide6364q2","for":"Slide6364q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10886","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide6364q2","for":"Slide6364q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6264","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6276","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6288","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6364","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_316","si6185","si6197","si6212","si6223","si6312","si6326","si6354","si10886","si6288"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6364"},"question":{"interactionId":"6165","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Contractors are responsible for disposing of all remaining hazardous chemicals or waste.\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_317","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_317","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6486","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","roles":{}},{"id":"si6387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","roles":{}},{"id":"si6399","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6411","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"Potential indoor air quality concerns can include: (select all that apply) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6422","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6426","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"Mold or mildew  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6422a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"22","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mold or mildew\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6437","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"Unsanitary conditions   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6433a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Unsanitary conditions\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6564","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6568","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Smoke ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6564a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Smoke\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6579","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6583","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Toxic gas or vapors ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6579a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Toxic gas or vapors\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6594","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Uncomfortable temperatures and/or humidity  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6594a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Uncomfortable temperatures and/or humidity\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6613","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Dust ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6609a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dust\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6624","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6628","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6624a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6556q3","for":"Slide6556q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6518","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide6556q3","for":"Slide6556q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6546","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide6556q3","for":"Slide6556q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10900","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide6556q3","for":"Slide6556q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6456","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6468","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6480","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6556","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_317","si6399","si6411","si6426","si6437","si6568","si6583","si6598","si6613","si6628","si6504","si6518","si6546","si10900","si6480"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6556"},"question":{"interactionId":"6379","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Potential indoor air quality concerns can include: (select all that apply)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["G"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_318","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_318","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6828","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","roles":{}},{"id":"si6674","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","roles":{}},{"id":"si6686","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6698","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"Interim life safety measures shall be instituted when: (select all that apply)  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6713","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"When exits are blocked and emergency traffic is re-routed.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6713","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6898q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si6709a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mold or mildew\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6720","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_49","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6724","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"When fire alarms systems, smoke detectors, sprinklers, and fire pumps are enabled.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6724","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6898q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si6720a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"When fire alarms systems, smoke detectors, sprinklers, and fire pumps are enabled.\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6731","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6735","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"When hot work permits are not required.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6735","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6898q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si6731a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"When hot work permits are not required.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6742","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6746","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"When vertical openings and/or penetrations are made through fire walls.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6746","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6898q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si6742a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"When vertical openings and/or penetrations are made through fire walls.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6898q4","for":"Slide6898q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide6898q4","for":"Slide6898q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6888","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_16","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide6898q4","for":"Slide6898q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide6898q4","for":"Slide6898q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6810","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6822","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6898","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_318","si6686","si6698","si6713","si6724","si6735","si6746","si6846","si6860","si6888","si10914","si6822"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6898"},"question":{"interactionId":"6666","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Interim life safety measures shall be instituted when: (select all that apply) \r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_319","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_319","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7062","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","roles":{}},{"id":"si6941","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","roles":{}},{"id":"si6953","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6965","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"When shall an Infection Control Risk Assessment (ICRA) be implemented? (select one)  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6976","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6980","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"To enable life safety measures.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6976a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To enable life safety measures.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6991","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_71","title":"To determine if the medicine you’re taking may effect your work.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6987a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To determine if the medicine you’re taking may effect your work.\r\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6998","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7002","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"To ensure hazardous energy sources have been isolated.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6998a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To ensure hazardous energy sources have been isolated.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7009","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_74","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7013","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":"To ensure the prevention and the control of infectious diseases that are linked to environmental disturbances by construction activities.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7009a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To ensure the prevention and the control of infectious diseases that are linked to environmental disturbances by construction activities.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si7080","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7132q5","for":"Slide7132q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide7132q5","for":"Slide7132q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_20","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide7132q5","for":"Slide7132q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide7132q5","for":"Slide7132q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7032","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7044","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_77","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7132","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_319","si6953","si6965","si6980","si6991","si7002","si7013","si7080","si7094","si7122","si10928","si7056"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7132"},"question":{"interactionId":"6933","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"When shall an Infection Control Risk Assessment (ICRA) be implemented? (select one) \r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_320","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_320","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7296","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_94","roles":{}},{"id":"si7175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","roles":{}},{"id":"si7187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7199","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"Smoking electronic cigarettes, e-cigarettes, or vaporizer cigarettes is allowed on SLCH campus. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7210","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7214","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7210a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"51","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_85","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":"False  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7221a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"53","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si7314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_21","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7366q6","for":"Slide7366q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7328","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide7366q6","for":"Slide7366q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7356","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_24","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide7366q6","for":"Slide7366q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10942","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide7366q6","for":"Slide7366q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7266","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_91","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7278","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7290","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7366","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_320","si7187","si7199","si7214","si7225","si7314","si7328","si7356","si10942","si7290"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7366"},"question":{"interactionId":"7167","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Smoking electronic cigarettes, e-cigarettes, or vaporizer cigarettes is allowed on SLCH campus.\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_321","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_321","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7902","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_127","roles":{}},{"id":"si7803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_117","roles":{}},{"id":"si7815","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_118","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7827","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_119","title":"Inspection of fall protection equipment must occur before each use. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7838","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_121","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7838a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si7849","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_122","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7853","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_123","title":"False  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7849a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"72","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7920","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_33","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7972q7","for":"Slide7972q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7934","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_34","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide7972q7","for":"Slide7972q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7962","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_36","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide7972q7","for":"Slide7972q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10970","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide7972q7","for":"Slide7972q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7872","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_124","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7884","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_125","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7896","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_126","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7972","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_321","si7815","si7827","si7842","si7853","si7920","si7934","si7962","si10970","si7896"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7972"},"question":{"interactionId":"7795","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Inspection of fall protection equipment must occur before each use.\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_322","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_322","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7488","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","roles":{}},{"id":"si7389","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","roles":{}},{"id":"si7401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7413","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":"What is the minimum number of weeks a contractor must give notice of a utility shut down to the Facility Operations Department? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7424","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7428","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_99","title":"1 week ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7424a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"60","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1 week\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7439","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"2 weeks  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7435a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"62","roles":{"answer":{"title":"2 weeks\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si7758","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7762","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3 weeks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7758a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"3 weeks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7773","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7777","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4 weeks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7773a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"4 weeks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7506","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_25","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7558q8","for":"Slide7558q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7520","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_26","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide7558q8","for":"Slide7558q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7548","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_28","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide7558q8","for":"Slide7558q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10956","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide7558q8","for":"Slide7558q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_103","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7558","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_322","si7401","si7413","si7428","si7439","si7762","si7777","si7506","si7520","si7548","si10956","si7482"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7558"},"question":{"interactionId":"7381","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"What is the minimum number of weeks a contractor must give notice of a utility shut down to the Facility Operations Department?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_323","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_142","roles":{}},{"id":"si8003","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_128","roles":{}},{"id":"si8015","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_129","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8027","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_130","title":"Access into any MRI control room and scanner is prohibited, unless escorted by SLCH radiology staff. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8038","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_131","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_132","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8038a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"75","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si8049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_133","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8053","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_134","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8049a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"77","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_37","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8194q9","for":"Slide8194q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8156","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_38","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide8194q9","for":"Slide8194q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_40","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide8194q9","for":"Slide8194q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide8194q9","for":"Slide8194q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_139","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_140","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_141","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8194","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_323","si8015","si8027","si8042","si8053","si8142","si8156","si8184","si10984","si8118"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8194"},"question":{"interactionId":"7995","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Access into any MRI control room and scanner is prohibited, unless escorted by SLCH radiology staff.\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_324","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_324","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_153","roles":{}},{"id":"si8217","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_143","roles":{}},{"id":"si8229","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_144","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8241","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_145","title":"Identify the three golden Hospital Safety Rules (HSRs):  (select one) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8252","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_146","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8256","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_147","title":"Intervene, Comply, Enforce  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8252a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"84","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intervene, Comply, Enforce\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8263","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_148","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8267","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_149","title":"Intervene, Conform, Encourage  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8263a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"86","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intervene, Conform, Encourage\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8394","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8398","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Intervene, Communicate, Encourage  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8394a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intervene, Communicate, Encourage\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si8409","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8413","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Intercede, Communicate, Encourage  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8409a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intercede, Communicate, Encourage\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8334","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_41","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8386q10","for":"Slide8386q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8348","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide8386q10","for":"Slide8386q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8376","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_44","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide8386q10","for":"Slide8386q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10998","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide8386q10","for":"Slide8386q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_150","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_151","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8310","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_152","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8386","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_324","si8229","si8241","si8256","si8267","si8398","si8413","si8334","si8348","si8376","si10998","si8310"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8386"},"question":{"interactionId":"8209","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Identify the three golden Hospital Safety Rules (HSRs): \r(select one)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_325","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8568","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_168","roles":{}},{"id":"si8447","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_154","roles":{}},{"id":"si8459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_155","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_156","title":"Concealed firearms may be brought into SLCH by the public even if the individual has a concealed carry permit. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_157","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8486","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_158","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8482a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"89","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_159","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8497","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_160","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8493a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"91","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si8586","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_45","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8638q11","for":"Slide8638q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8600","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_46","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide8638q11","for":"Slide8638q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8628","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_48","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide8638q11","for":"Slide8638q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11012","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide8638q11","for":"Slide8638q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8538","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_165","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8550","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_166","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_167","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8638","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_325","si8459","si8471","si8486","si8497","si8586","si8600","si8628","si11012","si8562"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8638"},"question":{"interactionId":"8439","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Concealed firearms may be brought into SLCH by the public even if the individual has a concealed carry permit.\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_326","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_326","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8760","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_179","roles":{}},{"id":"si8661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_169","roles":{}},{"id":"si8673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_170","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_171","title":"Shutdown notices sent to the SLCH Facility Operations Department include:  (select any or all that apply) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8696","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_172","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8700","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_173","title":"Electrical  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8696a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"98","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Electrical \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8707","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_174","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8711","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_175","title":"Hydraulic ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8707a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"100","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hydraulic\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8838","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8842","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Fire alarms, including sprinkler systems ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8838a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fire alarms, including sprinkler systems\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8853","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8857","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Pneumatic ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8853a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Pneumatic\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8872","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Chemical ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8868a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Chemical\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8883","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8887","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Thermal ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8883a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Thermal\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8898","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8902","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Mechanical ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8898a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mechanical\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8913","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8917","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8913a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si8778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_49","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8830q12","for":"Slide8830q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8792","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_50","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide8830q12","for":"Slide8830q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_52","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide8830q12","for":"Slide8830q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11026","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide8830q12","for":"Slide8830q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8730","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_176","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8742","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_177","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_178","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8830","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_326","si8673","si8685","si8700","si8711","si8842","si8857","si8872","si8887","si8902","si8917","si8778","si8792","si8820","si11026","si8754"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8830"},"question":{"interactionId":"8653","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Shutdown notices sent to the SLCH Facility Operations Department include:  (select any or all that apply)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["H"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_202","roles":{}},{"id":"si8967","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_180","roles":{}},{"id":"si8979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_181","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8991","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_182","title":"Questions and/or changes to the risk assessment shall be routed through the EHS Department via email. (select one) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9002","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_183","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9006","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_184","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9002a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"103","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9013","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_185","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9017","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_186","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9013a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"105","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si9150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_53","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9202q13","for":"Slide9202q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9164","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_54","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide9202q13","for":"Slide9202q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_56","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide9202q13","for":"Slide9202q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide9202q13","for":"Slide9202q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_199","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9114","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_200","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_201","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9202","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_327","si8979","si8991","si9006","si9017","si9150","si9164","si9192","si11040","si9126"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9202"},"question":{"interactionId":"8959","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Questions and/or changes to the risk assessment shall be routed through the EHS Department via email. (select one)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_328","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9324","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_213","roles":{}},{"id":"si9225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_203","roles":{}},{"id":"si9237","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_204","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9249","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_205","title":"The Infection Prevention Department will be notified prior to ALL above ceiling investigations. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9260","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_206","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9264","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_207","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9260a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"120","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si9271","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_208","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9275","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_209","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9271a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9342","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_57","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9394q14","for":"Slide9394q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9356","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_58","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide9394q14","for":"Slide9394q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9384","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_60","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide9394q14","for":"Slide9394q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11054","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide9394q14","for":"Slide9394q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_210","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9306","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_211","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9318","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_212","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9394","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_328","si9237","si9249","si9264","si9275","si9342","si9356","si9384","si11054","si9318"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9394"},"question":{"interactionId":"9217","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"The Infection Prevention Department will be notified prior to ALL above ceiling investigations.\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9516","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_224","roles":{}},{"id":"si9417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_214","roles":{}},{"id":"si9429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_215","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_216","title":"Tools can NEVER be left unattended in the hospital. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9452","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_217","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9456","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_218","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9452a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"125","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si9463","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_219","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9467","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_220","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9463a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"127","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9534","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_61","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9586q15","for":"Slide9586q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9548","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_62","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide9586q15","for":"Slide9586q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9576","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_64","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide9586q15","for":"Slide9586q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11068","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide9586q15","for":"Slide9586q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9486","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_221","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9498","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_222","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9510","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_223","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9586","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_329","si9429","si9441","si9456","si9467","si9534","si9548","si9576","si11068","si9510"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9586"},"question":{"interactionId":"9409","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Tools can NEVER be left unattended in the hospital.\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_330","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_330","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9708","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_235","roles":{}},{"id":"si9609","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_225","roles":{}},{"id":"si9621","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_226","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9633","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_227","title":"Before entering a confined space, the Supervisor must: (select any or all that apply) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9644","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_228","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9648","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_229","title":"Confirm that a valid permit is in place.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9644a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Confirm that a valid permit is in place.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9655","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_230","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9659","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_231","title":"Confirm that a qualified Attendant is present.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9655a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9786","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9790","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Confirm gas testing is carried out per the work permit.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9786a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Confirm gas testing is carried out per the work permit.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9801","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9805","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Confirm that it is safe to start work.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9801a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Confirm that it is safe to start work.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9816","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All the above.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9816a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All the above.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si9726","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_65","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9778q16","for":"Slide9778q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9740","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_66","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide9778q16","for":"Slide9778q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9768","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_68","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide9778q16","for":"Slide9778q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11082","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide9778q16","for":"Slide9778q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9678","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_232","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9690","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_233","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9702","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_234","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9778","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_330","si9621","si9633","si9648","si9659","si9790","si9805","si9820","si9726","si9740","si9768","si11082","si9702"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9778"},"question":{"interactionId":"9601","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Before entering a confined space, the Supervisor must:\r(select any or all that apply)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9990","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_252","roles":{}},{"id":"si9858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_236","roles":{}},{"id":"si9870","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_237","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_238","title":"ILSM inspections will be completed ______  by the contractor when life safety is compromised or impaired during construction, renovation, and maintenance activities. (select one) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9893","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_239","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9897","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_240","title":"hourly ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9893a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"135","roles":{"answer":{"title":"hourly\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9904","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_241","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9908","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_242","title":"daily ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9904a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"137","roles":{"answer":{"title":"daily\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si9915","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_243","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9919","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_244","title":"weekly ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9915a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"139","roles":{"answer":{"title":"weekly\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_245","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_246","title":"monthly ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9926a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"141","roles":{"answer":{"title":"monthly\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10008","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_69","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10060q17","for":"Slide10060q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10022","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_70","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide10060q17","for":"Slide10060q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10050","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_72","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide10060q17","for":"Slide10060q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11096","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide10060q17","for":"Slide10060q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9960","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_249","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_250","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9984","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_251","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10060","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","si9870","si9882","si9897","si9908","si9919","si9930","si10008","si10022","si10050","si11096","si9984"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10060"},"question":{"interactionId":"9850","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"ILSM inspections will be completed ______  by the contractor when life safety is compromised or impaired during construction, renovation, and maintenance activities. (select one)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_332","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10212","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_267","roles":{}},{"id":"si10091","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_253","roles":{}},{"id":"si10103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_254","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_255","title":"Safety guards can be removed when a tool is being used.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_256","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10130","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_257","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10126a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"146","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10137","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_258","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10141","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_259","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10137a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"148","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si10230","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_73","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10282q18","for":"Slide10282q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10244","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_74","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide10282q18","for":"Slide10282q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_76","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide10282q18","for":"Slide10282q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide10282q18","for":"Slide10282q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_264","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_265","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_266","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10282","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_332","si10103","si10115","si10130","si10141","si10230","si10244","si10272","si11110","si10206"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10282"},"question":{"interactionId":"10083","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Safety guards can be removed when a tool is being used. \r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_333","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Be sure to Click Submit. When finished, click Next.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10404","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_278","roles":{}},{"id":"si10305","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_268","roles":{}},{"id":"si10317","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_269","title":"Safety Orientation Exam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_270","title":"Identify what unsafe conditions would require a stoppage of work while working within a construction containment area: (select any or all that apply) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10340","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_271","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10344","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_272","title":"The sticky mat is missing or needs to be replaced.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10340a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"155","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The sticky mat is missing or needs to be replaced.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_273","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10355","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_274","title":"The seal around the containment wall (i.e. ceiling, floor, and walls) is compromised.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10351a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"157","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The seal around the containment wall (i.e. ceiling, floor, and walls) is compromised.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10482","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10486","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The HEPA filter in the work space is not working or the filter is clogged.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10482a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The HEPA filter in the work space is not working or the filter is clogged.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Positive pressure is observed on the vaneometer.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10497a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Positive pressure is observed on the vaneometer.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10512","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10516","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Openings are discovered in the temporary plastic or hard partition.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10512a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Openings are discovered in the temporary plastic or hard partition.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10527","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10531","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All the above.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10527a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All the above. \r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si10422","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_77","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10474q19","for":"Slide10474q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10436","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_78","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide10474q19","for":"Slide10474q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10464","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_80","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide10474q19","for":"Slide10474q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11124","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide10474q19","for":"Slide10474q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10374","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_275","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_276","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_277","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10474","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_333","si10317","si10329","si10344","si10355","si10486","si10501","si10516","si10531","si10422","si10436","si10464","si11124","si10398"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10474"},"question":{"interactionId":"10297","quizId":458,"title":"Safety Orientation Exam\r","text":"Identify what unsafe conditions would require a stoppage of work while working within a construction containment area:\r(select any or all that apply)\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["F"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5741","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5749","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5757","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5765","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5781","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10614","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5730","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5745","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5753","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5761","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5777","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attempts: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5785","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5789","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5803","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10625","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Retake Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"retake","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5720","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5720"}}},{"id":"Widget_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Widget_4","roles":{"interaction":{"type":"Not implemented","title":"Not implemented","categories":[]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_284","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_284","title":"Please print this certificate and return it to the SLCH Facilities Department to receive your 2017 Contractor Safety Orientation Badge. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_285","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_285","title":"Congratulations!   You have passed the quiz! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_334","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Use this Print button: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10808","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_284","Text_Caption_285","Text_Caption_334"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10808"}}},{"id":"2017 SLCH Contractor Orientation","class":"project","title":"2017 SLCH Contractor Orientation","children":["Slide4607","Slide4619","Slide4631","Slide4643","Slide4655","Slide4667","Slide4679","Slide4691","Slide4703","Slide4715","Slide4727","Slide4739","Slide4751","Slide4763","Slide4775","Slide4787","Slide4799","Slide4811","Slide4823","Slide4835","Slide4847","Slide4859","Slide4871","Slide4883","Slide4895","Slide5556","Slide11464","Slide6364","Slide6556","Slide6898","Slide7132","Slide7366","Slide7972","Slide7558","Slide8194","Slide8386","Slide8638","Slide8830","Slide9202","Slide9394","Slide9586","Slide9778","Slide10060","Slide10282","Slide10474","Slide5720","Slide10808"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide5556q0","Slide11464q1","Slide6364q2","Slide6556q3","Slide6898q4","Slide7132q5","Slide7366q6","Slide7972q7","Slide7558q8","Slide8194q9","Slide8386q10","Slide8638q11","Slide8830q12","Slide9202q13","Slide9394q14","Slide9586q15","Slide9778q16","Slide10060q17","Slide10282q18","Slide10474q19"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":200,"passScore":160}}}],"toc":[{"id":"Slide4607","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide4619","title":"Safety is Everyone’s Business "},{"id":"Slide4631","title":"SLCH Golden Rules "},{"id":"Slide4643","title":"Hospital Safety Rules (HSRs) "},{"id":"Slide4655","title":"WORKING WITH A CURRENT RISK ASSESSMENT "},{"id":"Slide4667","title":"INFECTION CONTROL "},{"id":"Slide4679","title":"LIFE SAFETY "},{"id":"Slide4691","title":"HOT WORK "},{"id":"Slide4703","title":"HAZARDOUS ENERGY SOURCES "},{"id":"Slide4715","title":"TOOL SAFETY "},{"id":"Slide4727","title":"CONFINED SPACES "},{"id":"Slide4739","title":"TEMPORARY CONTAINMENT AREAS "},{"id":"Slide4751","title":"MRI SAFETY "},{"id":"Slide4763","title":"WORKING FROM HEIGHTS "},{"id":"Slide4775","title":"INDOOR AIR QUALITY "},{"id":"Slide4787","title":"EMERGENCY NOTIFICATION "},{"id":"Slide4799","title":"HAZARD COMMUNICATION "},{"id":"Slide4811","title":"HAZARDOUS MATERIALS AND WASTE "},{"id":"Slide4823","title":"BLOODBORNE PATHOGENS "},{"id":"Slide4835","title":"NO SMOKING "},{"id":"Slide4847","title":"NO DRUGS OR ALCOHOL "},{"id":"Slide4859","title":"NO WEAPONS "},{"id":"Slide4871","title":"KEY SLCH CONTACTS "},{"id":"Slide4883","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide4895","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide5556","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide11464","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide6364","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide6556","title":"Slide 29"},{"id":"Slide6898","title":"Slide 30"},{"id":"Slide7132","title":"Slide 31"},{"id":"Slide7366","title":"Slide 32"},{"id":"Slide7972","title":"Slide 33"},{"id":"Slide7558","title":"Slide 34"},{"id":"Slide8194","title":"Slide 35"},{"id":"Slide8386","title":"Slide 36"},{"id":"Slide8638","title":"Slide 37"},{"id":"Slide8830","title":"Slide 38"},{"id":"Slide9202","title":"Slide 39"},{"id":"Slide9394","title":"Slide 40"},{"id":"Slide9586","title":"Slide 41"},{"id":"Slide9778","title":"Slide 42"},{"id":"Slide10060","title":"Slide 43"},{"id":"Slide10282","title":"Slide 44"},{"id":"Slide10474","title":"Slide 45"},{"id":"Slide5720","title":"Slide 46"},{"id":"Slide10808","title":"Slide 47"}]}